glowing.com 2019-12-10

# Glow - Privacy

Last Updated: June 14, 2018 

Glow takes issues of privacy and the protection not only of personal health information, but all kinds of information about your private life very seriously. As discussed below we take great efforts to protect your information from disclosure, to use your information only to provide services to you, to improve the service for you, to improve our ability to provide services to other people in a similar situation, and to assist researchers in finding better ways to improve health. 

WE DO NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL DATA TO THIRD PARTIES. WE DON’T SHARE YOUR INFORMATION (OTHER THAN FORUM POSTS) TO SOCIAL NETWORKS OR OTHER PUBLIC OR SEMI-PUBLIC PLACES UNLESS INSTRUCTED BY YOU TO DO SO. 

We only disclose your information to you or as you authorize us to (although we may include certain elements of that information in our data base on an anonymized basis). However we wish to remind you that the kind of information Glow collects is significantly more sensitive than the information you may be providing to other application providers – and you should be extra careful before instructing us to share that information with anyone else. Your menstrual cycles, fertility information and pregnancy status is much more sensitive than the number of steps you took today or where you were when you took your most recent selfie – we recognize that and recommend that you take extra care before deciding to ask us to share it with anyone. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, it is a material part of the contractual agreement between you and Upward Labs Holdings, Inc. (“Glow”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy and not defined herein shall have the definitions provided in our Terms of Use Agreement or in our Glow Fertility Patient Services Agreement, if applicable. This Privacy Policy describes the ways we collect, protect, use and store your personal data. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us. 

##  PARTICULARLY IMPORTANT INFORMATION 

Who We are: For the purpose of applicable data protection legislation, the data controller of your personal data is Upward Lab Holdings, Inc. of 555 Kearny Street, 7th Floor San Francisco, California. We are in the process of identifying and appointing a Representative in the EU, but in the meantime, our EU Representative is Jirong Wang, reachable through EURepresentative@glowing.com. Our data protection officer is Jirong Wang, reachable through GlowDataProtectionOfficer@glowing.com 

Must Read Sections: We direct your attention in particular to the sections entitled “International Data Transfer” and “Your Rights”. 

##  Changes to the Privacy Policy. 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a revised copy to our website, Glowing.com (“Website”) or through our applications, including Glow, Glow Baby, Glow Nurture, Eve (Eve by Glow), GlowCare (collectively the “Glow Apps”), and we encourage you to review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will alert you through a notice on the Glow Apps, on our Website, or through an email prior to such change(s) taking effect. The “Last Updated” legend above indicates when this Privacy Policy was last changed. 

##  PURPOSES OF PROCESSING 

We collect information about you in a range of forms, including personal data. As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal data” is as defined in the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 and any successor legislation, which includes any information which, either alone or in combination with other information we hold about you, identifies you as an individual, including, for example, your name, postal address, email address and telephone number, and in the case of Glow, includes “Sensitive Personal Data.” 

We will only process your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws. We need certain personal data in order to provide you with access to certain parts of the Website and to access the Glow Apps and any other of our products or services (collectively, the “Services”). If you created a profile/registered with us through the Services or the Website on a mobile device or through any other means, you will have been asked to tick a box to agree to the use and disclosure of your personal data as outlined below. This consent provides us with the legal basis we require under applicable law to process your data. You maintain the right to withdraw such consent at any time. Furthermore, Glow’s Services may require you to share Sensitive Personal Data (defined below) with us, for which we will seek separate consent. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use Agreement and, if applicable, our Glow Fertility Patient Services Agreement, do not use any of the Glow Apps or the Website or any of the Services. 

##  WHAT WE COLLECT 

##  Information You Give Us: 

Glow gives you a number of options regarding what information you will give us: 

• When you register to create an account with Glow and/or Glow First (whether through one of the Glow Apps or on the Internet); 

• When you participate on a Forum or other communication mechanism; and 

• When you update a Glow App or the Website with information relevant to your fertility or pregnancy, 

When you register with Glow you will submit a variety of personal data (such as gender, age, birthdate, name, email address, mobile phone number) and as you use the Glow Apps you may submit a variety of information (such as menstrual cycle, weight, temperature, occupation, hobbies, interests, zip code, etc.) which may include sensitive personal data about personal health issues and/or information related to your past, present, or future physical or mental health condition (“Sensitive Personal Data”). You may also choose to provide us with access to certain personal data stored by third parties including social media sites (such as Facebook and Twitter) and health sites, such as Apple HealthKit and Google Fit. The information we have access to varies by site and is controlled by your privacy settings on that site and your authorization. You may (and may be required to) share information about or give us access to additional third-party websites or services. 

If you establish a GlowCare account / register to use GlowCare we will share personal data including Sensitive Perosnal Data with your healthcare provider that is using GlowCare. 

Also, when you sign up for Glow First, we may collect personal data such as credit card numbers and/or cell phone numbers, as well as other information about you necessary to ensure that a transaction is properly authorized, such as your address, zip code, and cv number (collectively, “Payment Information”). We also may retain such Payment Information (or our third party “fulfillment house”, such as PayPal, may retain such information) to facilitate future transactions. See “Controlling Your Personal Data” below if you would like us not to use that information to assist you in completing future transactions. 

If you choose to participate in Glow First or become a party to the Glow Fertility Services Patient Agreement, not only may you need to provide us with Payment Information, but if you become entitled to receive a payment from Glow First, you will need to provide us with your social security number as well as information about an accredited infertility clinic and proof of medical claims showing that you are using their services. We may use that information in making filings with the IRS or relevant state taxing authorities. 

By agreeing to the Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement and this Privacy Policy you are authorizing the connections between our Services and your records and our using your personal data as described herein and therein. Upon your affirmative acceptance of the Glow HIPAA Authorization Form and the Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, you authorize Glow to use all such personal data, including data that may relate to HIV and/or other sexually transmitted diseases, mental and behavioral health conditions and treatment, substance abuse conditions and treatment, and other Sensitive Personal Data, throughout the term of your use of the Services, to store such data as described herein, and to store it using our HIPAA compliant policies and use it only as described in this Privacy Policy or the Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, as required or permitted by law, even once you are no longer using the Service. You may revoke such authorization with respect to data we have not yet obtained by contacting us as described below. 

##  User Generated Content 

In addition to information about yourself, it may be possible for you to submit other content ("Content"), such as photos and other media, each of which you present through technology available through the Services, including but not limited to our forum. It is entirely up to you whether you want to submit this additional information, and whether you would like to make it available to others – although information you share on the forum will automatically be shared with others, including users of the Services and others on the internet. However, Glow has no responsibility for how people you allow to view your Content (or the public if you make any information available to the public or post on the forum) use that material, or to whom they may forward it. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your personal data, or any other information, on the forum. Such personal data and other information will not be private or confidential once it is published on the forum. 

If you send or disclose any Sensitive Personal Data to us when you submit user generated content on our forum, you consent to our processing and use of such Sensitive Personal Data in accordance with this Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such Sensitive Personal Data, you must not submit such user generated content to our Website.” 

Finally, we may use information that you include in emails or other communication methods to us to assist us in providing the Service, and we may publish that information on an anonymous basis. Please note also that by accepting our Terms of Use Agreement, you have agreed that the text of any posting on any one of the forums, bulletin boards, or other similar publically accessible systems offered by Glow (including any market place or wish list) may be used and republished by Glow in its sole discretion and will be made available to other people through the internet. 

In each case, we will collect and record the information you have provided. 

##  Information We Automatically Collect: 

If you visit this Website, be advised that Company will maintain web logs to record data about all visitors and customers who use this website and interact with the Services and we will store this information. All web logs are stored securely and are accessible to a very limited number of employees who are required to adhere to strict guidelines regarding user data security and privacy. 

Furthermore, when you use one of the Glow Apps, we may record information regarding the use of that Glow App, including your cell phone number, and if such facilities are enabled on your cell phone, your location and similar information. 

Finally, in order to provide the best possible service and to allow us to make certain internal reports and make recommendations, we collect aggregate information about the use of the Service, including information about users accessing this website or using the Glow Apps, such as Internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time (“Activity Information”). 

When you visit the Services, we may also store information based on your usage history. This includes, but is not limited to, details of your transactions, content you viewed, click stream information, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. We use various technologies to collect and store information which may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. Please refer to the section on cookies below. 

##  Information We Collect From Other Sources: 

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal data stored by third parties. The information we have access to varies by site and is controlled by your privacy settings on that site and your authorization. You may (and in order to use certain services may be required to) share information about or give us access to additional third-party websites or services. Should you do so, you agree that Glow may collect, store and use this information in ways consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Information from Social Networking Sites. Our Services include interfaces that allow you to connect with social networking sites (each a “SNS”). If you connect to a SNS through our Services, you authorize us to access, use and store the information that you agreed the SNS could provide to us based on your settings on that SNS. We will access, use and store that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can revoke our access to the information you provide in this way at any time by amending the appropriate settings from within your account settings on the applicable SNS. 

Information from Health Sites. Our Services include interfaces that allow you to connect with health sites, such as Google Fit or Apple Fit. We may add this to information we get from our Services. Please refer to the section “Information Shared with Other Systems, Such As Healthkit or Google Fit” below for more information. 

## HOW WE USE/SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We may use personal data to verify your identity, verify your address, or manage risk. We may also use personal data to perform and improve our Services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for medical research. For example, we may use information to provide customer service and support, process transactions, resolve disputes, collect payments, prevent illegal activities, customize the Services and recommendations, reduce risk to all parties involved in our transactions, and verify the accuracy of information. 

WE DO NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL DATA TO THIRD PARTIES. WE DON’T SHARE YOUR INFORMATION (OTHER THAN FORUM POSTS) TO SOCIAL NETWORKS OR OTHER PUBLIC OR SEMI-PUBLIC PLACES UNLESS INSTRUCTED BY YOU TO DO SO. However, we may share your personal information with third parties and an aggregate and anonymous format combined with the information we collect from other users for research and/or academic purposes only. We may share your personal information as necessary for Glow to provide you Services, and possibly to tell you about products and services of interest to you (subject, in the case of EU residents, to your consent to receipt of such communications). to fulfill your service request; to third-party fulfillment houses, customer support, billing and credit verification services, and the like; to comply with tax and other applicable law; as otherwise expressly permitted by this privacy policy or glow’s terms of use agreement, located at https://www.glowing.com/tos, or as otherwise authorized by you. You should also note that glow does not guarantee the security of any of your private transmissions against unauthorized or unlawful interception or access by third parties. 

We make your profile available to other users according to the privacy settings you set for yourself as part of your profile. Your user name will be identified to us and to any recipient of messages you send through the Services, including on forums. We also use your name, email address and other information on our system to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. In the event that we decide to allow you to submit other information about yourself, the availability of that information to other users will also be controlled by privacy settings you may set for yourself. 

We share your personal data with employees and affiliates, as well as certain vendors, partners and third parties as required to offer the Services. This includes, but is not limited to, processing transactions, maintaining your account, responding to court orders and legal investigations, for litigation purposes, complying with audits or other investigations, and reporting to credit bureaus. We do not profit from your personal information and do not share your information with advertisers. 

We may combine your personal data with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Services, content, and communications with you. We may also do so in order to improve our prediction methodologies and algorithms. 

##  Anonymous Data 

We may combine your personal data with information we collect from other users in an aggregate and anonymous format and share this anonymous data with third parties. When we use the term “anonymous data,” we are referring to data and information that does not permit you to be identified or identifiable, either alone or when combined with any other information available to a third party. We may create anonymous data from the personal data we receive about you and other individuals whose personal data we collect. Anonymous data might include analytics information and information collected by us using cookies. We make personal data into anonymous data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We do this in order to improve the quality of the information we provide to you and to other users. 

##  Protected Health Information 

We maintain “protected health information” (as defined in the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act, “HIPAA”) in compliance with applicable health care privacy and security rules and our contractual obligations with our business partners and customers, including health care providers and their contractors (who are also subject to HIPAA). In the case where you affirmatively accept our Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, and/or where your healthcare provider uses GlowCare and you establish an account on GlowCare, we act as a conduit between (a) health care providers offering fertility-related services, (b) other persons involved in the arranging, provision or financing of health care services and (c) end users such as you, and share your protected health information in connection with those services only in accordance with applicable law. 

##  Marketing 

We may use personal data to deliver products, or service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences. With your consent (either in response to an email request or in certain cases, pursuant to the preferences you’ve expressed in your profile), we may send you marketing e-mails about upcoming promotions, and other news, including information about products and services that may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving such information at any time: such marketing emails tell you how to “opt-out.” Please note, even if you opt out of receiving marketing emails, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your account with us (if you have one) and our business dealings with you. We may combine your information (after it has been anonymized) with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Services, content and advertising. We may also do so in order to improve our prediction methodologies and algorithms. 

##  Third Party Content 

Glow may use information derived from your use of the Services to determine what content we believe may be of interest to you, including content from the providers of goods and services (who may pay us to show you such content) that you may be able to purchase through the Services or otherwise. We do not provide any personal data to third-party content providers. Note, however, that if a third party content provider asks us to show content to users with certain characteristics (for example, women ages 18- 24) or a segment of that group (for example, women ages 18-24 who have indicated they are trying to conceive) and you respond to that content or click on links embedded in that content, the third-party content provider may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience that they are trying to reach. Glow does not have access to or control over cookies, web beacons, or other technologies that third parties who have asked us to show you content may use, and the privacy practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy. Please contact these companies directly for information on their data collection and privacy practices. For more information on available opt-out options for targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks, see http://www.networkadvertising.org/. 

##  Affiliates 

We may decide to share information about your transactions and experiences using the Glow Service (but not about your creditworthiness) to our affiliates for their everyday business purposes. 

##  Corporate Restructuring 

In the event that all or a part of our business or assets are sold or transferred or we merge with another company your personal data may be transferred to the buyer/surviving party, but this privacy policy will continue to control that person’s use of your personal information. 

##  Other Disclosures 

We will share your information with any party when required by law or by a government request to do so or to combat fraud or criminal activity. 

You understand and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose any information we may have about you (including personal data and protected health information) and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process (for example, we may disclose your information as necessary to comply with an authorized civil, criminal or regulatory investigation), such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of our affiliates or the public. Glow is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that it receives. We reserve the right to release personal data or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy or the Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate the Glow Apps, our Website or to protect our rights or property, or that of our affiliates, or our officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful. If we are legally compelled to disclose information about you to a third party, we will attempt to notify you by sending an email to the email address in our records unless doing so would violate the law or unless you have not provided your email address to us. 

We also use anonymous data and certain technical information about your computer and/or smartphone and your access of the Services (including your Internet protocol address) in order to operate, maintain and manage the Services. Glow may disclose that kind of information to its partners in order to provide the Services, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Services, to communicate with you about the Services, and to enhance your experience on the Services. However, we do not give our partners an independent right to share this information. Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Services, however, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing such information (whether personal data or other information) with these third parties. Glow, certain of its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the content that you upload to the Services in order to provide the Services and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

##  CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

Be advised that if you send messages or post material on or forums or elsewhere containing personal data, that data may be collected and used by others. The Services provide a number of tools that you can use to control the availability of your profile and other personal data, but forum posts will be available to the general public. You can edit your profile and other data at any time through each of the Glow Apps and/or the Website. 

You can terminate your account at any time, which will remove your profile and other personal data from view. Glow, however, may (but is not obligated to) keep information about you that is on its system following your termination, and your forum posts will continue to be available online. You may request complete deletion of your personal data (other than forum posts) by writing feedback@glowing.com. Subject to the provisions of your Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, if any, we will delete your data within 60 days of our receipt of that request. Contact Glow at feedback@glowing.com to terminate your account or for any other questions about your personal data and/or forum posts. Unless you request the deletion of your personal information and subject to applicable law, Glow maintain copies of your content indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. 

##  INFORMATION SHARED WITH OTHER SYSTEMS, SUCH AS HEALTHKIT OR GOOGLE FIT 

You may instruct us to share certain of your personal data (including Sensitive Personal Data) with systems such as Apple’s Healthkit or Google Fit, and to access personal data from those systems which we will use to improve the services we provide to you and, we hope, make our information more accurate for you as an individual. Before you tell us to share your information with another system, however, you should review the applicable privacy policy of that system, since any information you have instructed us to share will become subject to those policies (Apple’s policy can be found at https://www.apple.com/privacy/privacy-policy/) and Google’s Privacy Policy can be found at http://www.google.com/intl/en_us/policies/privacy/). 

In addition, in the event that you use one of those services, you should be careful about allowing other applications, services or people to access your information through that service. While much information collected by those services is innocuous, people who see Glow data may be able to determine a variety of personal data, such as that you are trying to become pregnant or when you are likely to be having your period. 

Glow does not use or disclose to third parties personal data or other information gained through the use of the HealthKit framework or Google Fit for advertising, other use-based data mining purposes or similar services, other than for purposes of improving health or for purposes of health or medical research. 

We do not disclose any of your personal data, to any third party without your express permission (other than as provided herein or in anonymized and aggregated format), and in the case of information gained through HealthKit or Google Fit such sharing will only be for purposes of enabling the third party to provide health and/or fitness services or for medical research. 

We do not sell any of your personal data, including personal data gained through HealthKit or Google Fit, to advertising platforms, data brokers or information resellers. 

We do not use any of the personal data obtained through HealthKit or Google Fit for any purpose other than providing health and/or fitness services in connection with the Glow Apps. 

##  OTHERS’ INFORMATION 

You may decide to provide us with another person's email address so that person may be invited to join Glow or so that we may facilitate your communication with other people through the Services. You may also provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through the Glow Apps. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join Glow or receive content through one of the Glow Apps. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from Glow. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above. 

##  AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING AND PROFILING 

We do not generally use your personal data for the purposes of automated decision-making. However, we may do so in order to fulfill obligations imposed by law, in which case we will inform you of any such processing and provide you with an opportunity to object. 

##  COOKIES 

The Service sends "cookies" to your computer or smartphone when you access the Website or use one of the Glow Apps and the Services use such cookies as described here. A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive or smartphone that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or your use of the Services, such as the domain name of the user, your internet service provider, your operating system, and the date and time of access. We may obtain the services of outside parties to assist us in collecting and processing information collected through cookies. 

You can set your browser or mobile device to notify you when you receive a cookie. This will enable you to decide if you want to accept it or not. If you do not accept cookies you may not be able to use all functionality of your browser software, the Website or the Glow Apps. Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org 

The Services use the following types of cookies for the purposes set out below: 

Type of cookie | Purpose   
---|---  
Essential Cookies  |  These cookies are essential to provide you with services available through the Services and to enable you to use some of its features. For example, they allow you to log in to secure areas of the Website and help the content of the pages you request load quickly. Without these cookies, the Services that you have asked for cannot be provided, and we only use these cookies to provide you with those Services.   
Functionality Cookies  |  These cookies allow the Services to remember choices you make when you use the Services, such as remembering certain preferences, remembering your login details and remembering the changes you make to other parts of the Website or the Glow Apps which you can customize. The purpose of these cookies is to provide you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-enter your preferences every time you visit the Website or use the Services.   
Analytics and Performance Cookies  |  These cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our Services and how users use our Services. The information gathered does not identify any individual visitor. It includes the number of visitors to the Services, the websites that referred them to our Services, the pages they visited on our Services, what time of day they visited our Services, whether they have visited our Services before, and other similar information. We use this information to help operate our Services more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information and to monitor the level of activity on our Services. 

We use Google Analytics for this purpose, which uses its own cookies. You can find more information about [Google Analytics cookies here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage).   
  
Targeted and advertising cookies  |  We do not use Targeted Advertising cookies.   
Social Media Cookies  |  These cookies are used when you share information using a social media sharing button or “like” button on our Services or you link your account or engage with our content on or through a social networking website such as Facebook or Twitter. The social network will record that you have done this.   
  
If you would like more information about cookies associated with on-line advertising or to opt-out of third-party collection of this information, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative website http://www.networkadvertising.org. You can also disable cookies that remember your browsing habits and target advertising at you by visiting http://www.youronlinechoises.com/uk/your-ad-choice. If you choose to remove targeted or advertising cookies, you will still see advertisements but they may not be relevant to you. Also, even if you do choose to remove cookies by the companies listed at the above links, not all companies that serve online behavioral advertising are included in this list, and so you may still receive some cookies and tailored advertisements from companies that are not listed. 

We may also use internet tags (also known as action tags, web beacons, single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs and 1-by-1 GIFs) and cookies at our Website and in the Glow Apps and may deploy these tags/cookies through a third-party advertising partner or a web analytical service partner and we or they may store the respective information (including your IP address) in a foreign country. These tags/cookies may be placed both on online advertisements that bring users to our Website and on different pages of our Website or the Glow Apps. We use this technology to measure the visitors' responses to our Website and the Glow Apps and the effectiveness of communications with users (from ourselves and third parties) including how many times a page is opened and which information is consulted, as well as to evaluate your use of our Website or the Glow Apps. A third-party partner or the web analytical service partner may be able to collect data about visitors to our and other sites because of these internet tags/cookies, may compose reports regarding our Website’s and the Glow Apps’ activity for us and may provide further services which are related to the use of the Glow Apps, our Website and the internet. They may provide such information to other parties if there is a legal requirement that they do so, or if they hire the other parties to process information on their behalf. If you would like more information about web tags and cookies associated with on-line advertising or to opt-out of third-party collection of this information, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative website http://www.networkadvertising.org. (We are not affiliated with the Networking Advertising Initiative in any way.) 

##  THIRD PARTY SITES 

The Services may contain links to other web sites, and content in the Glow Apps may be hosted by other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal data. It is up to you to review those policies yourself. 

##  INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFER 

Your information, including personal data that we collect from you, may be transferred to, stored at and processed by us outside the country in which you reside, including, but not limited to the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world. By using the Glow Apps or Services you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. 

##  SECURITY 

We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect personal data within our organization. If you have any questions regarding which measures and techniques we use, feel free to contact us. Unfortunately, no transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be completely secure, and transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us using the details set forth in the section titled “Additional Questions” below. 

In addition, we urge you to take precautionary measures in maintaining the integrity of your data. Please be responsible in making sure no one can see or has access to your personal accounts and log-in username and password information. If you use a public computer, such as one at a library or a university, or a shared device, always remember to log out of the Glow Apps or Services. 

If you use the Glow Apps or Services through your employer’s computer network a mobile device owned by your employer or through an internet café, library or other potentially non-secure internet connection, such use is at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check beforehand with each such company’s privacy and security policy with respect to Internet and mobile device use. 

We cannot guarantee the identity of any other person with whom you may interact in the course of using the Glow Apps or Services, or the authenticity of any information that others may provide. 

Company is not responsible for your handling, sharing, re-sharing and/or distribution of your personal health information. Moreover, if you forward personal health information electronically to another person on or off any Glow Apps or the Services, we are not responsible for any harm or other consequences from third party use or re-sharing of your information. 

##  RETENTION 

We will only retain your personal data as long reasonably required for you to use the Glow Apps and/or to provide you with the Services unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (for example for regulatory purposes). You may request that we delete data you have provided by sending an email to support@glowing.com. Subject to the provisions of your Glow Fertility Program Patient Services Agreement, if any, we will delete your data within 60 days of our receipt of that request. 

##  CHILDREN 

We do not knowingly allow individual Users who are identified as located in the European Economic Area and under the age of 16 or who are identified as located outside the European Economic Area and under the age of 13 to create accounts that allow access to our secure site or that use Glow Apps, without them obtaining the prior consent of a parent or guardian. 

##  YOUR RIGHTS 

  * Opt-out. You may contact us anytime to opt-out of: (i) direct marketing communications; (ii) automated decision-making and/or profiling; (iii) our collection of Sensitive Personal Data; (iv) any new processing of your personal data that we may carry out beyond the original purpose; or (v) the transfer of your personal data from a server or business located in the European Economic Area to a server or business outside the European Economic Area. Please note that your use of some of the Glow Apps or Services may be ineffective upon opt-out. 
  * Access. You may access the information we hold about you at any time via your profile/account or by contacting us directly. 
  * Amend. You can also contact us to update or correct any inaccuracies in your personal data. 
  * Move. Your personal data is portable – i.e. you to have the flexibility to move your data to other service providers as you wish. 
  * Erase and forget. In certain situations, for example when the information we hold about you is no longer relevant or is incorrect, you can request that we erase your data. 

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the details set forth in the section titled “Additional Questions” below. In your request, please make clear: (i) what personal data is concerned; and (ii) which of the above rights you would like to enforce. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the personal data associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable and in any event, within one month of your request. Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion. 

##  COMPLAINTS 

We are committed to resolve any complaints about our collection or use of your personal data. If you would like to make a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices in relation to your personal data, please contact us at: privacy@glowing.com. We will reply to your complaint as soon as we can and in any event, within 45 days. We hope to resolve any complaint brought to our attention, however if you feel that your complaint has not been adequately resolved, you reserve the right to contact your local data protection supervisory authority. 

##  ADDITIONAL QUESTIONS 

Again, feel free to contact us by sending an email to info@glowing.com, any time, if you have further questions about Glow or this Privacy Policy. 

Please contact legal@glowing.com if you would like to receive a copy of this document showing changes from previous versions. 

##  HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us at info@glowing.com
